A Guide to the National Committee on United States-China Relations records, RG 1, Accession 1 FA772
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Publications and Reports, 6
  - National Committee on United States - China Relations Annual Reports, 1998-2000 (Box 143, Folder 2134)
  - National Committee on United States - China Relations Annual Reports, 2001-2003 (Box 143, Folder 2135)
    Includes 2 copies of each report. The NCUSCR's thirty-fifth anniversary was in 2001.
  - National Committee on United States - China Relations Annual Reports, 2004-2007 (Box 143, Folder 2136)
    Includes 2 copies of each report (2004-2005, 2006, and 2007). The NCUSCR's fortieth-anniversary was in 2006.
  - National Committee on United States - China Relations Annual Reports, 2008-2010 (Box 144, Folder 2137)
    Includes 2 copies of the 2008 and 2010 reports. There is only a color photocopy of the 2009 report.
  - National Committee on United States - China Relations Annual Reports, 2011-2013 (Box 144, Folder 2138)
    Includes 2 copies of each report. The NCUSCR's forty-fifth anniversary was in 2011.
  - Notes from the National Committee, Volumes 1-4, 1970-1974 (Box 144, Folder 2139)
    File includes two copies of most issues.
  - Notes from the National Committee, Volumes 5-7, 1975-1977 (Box 144, Folder 2140)
  - Notes from the National Committee, Volumes 8-12, 1978-1982 (Box 144, Folder 2141)
  - Notes from the National Committee, Volumes 13-17, 1983-1989 (Box 144, Folder 2142)
  - Notes from the National Committee, Volumes 18-22, 1989-1993 (Box 144, Folder 2143)
  - Notes from the National Committee, Volumes 23-25, 1994-1996 (Box 145, Folder 2144)
  - Notes from the National Committee, Volumes 26-28, 1997-1999 (Box 145, Folder 2145)
  - Notes from the National Committee, Volumes 29-31, 2000-2002 (Box 145, Folder 2146)
  - Notes from the National Committee, Volumes 32-34, 2003-2006 (Box 145, Folder 2147)
    For volume 33, have number 1 only.
  - Notes from the National Committee, Volumes 35, 37, 2008-2010 (Box 145, Folder 2148)
    No volume 36; volume 37, number 1 only.
  - Corporate Notes, Volumes 1-2, 1992-1993 (Box 145, Folder 2149)
    Volume 1, numbers 1-3, 5-6; volume 2, numbers 1-2.